# James Ciclitira

Product Designer based in London, creating complex digital products that lead to better user experiences. I love to design beautifully simple interfaces, code, iterate and create. I am an experienced and capable Digital Product Designer with over two years' professional experience.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Product Designer**

CrowdScores · September 2015 - January 2017

CrowdScores is a real-time sports data application. I had the pleasure of working as the principal designer, taking responsibility for a variety of roles. Responsibilities included improving the existing product, researching and developing new features, conceptualising ideas and prototyping.

### **Product & Web Development**

Suggestv · January 2017 - April 2017

Suggestv is the inventor of semantic video distribution. I was responsible for designing and facilitating the production of a semantic video distribution platform using React.

## Freelance Designer

Prediction labs · January 2017 - Present

Numilli app - Bitcoin safe and easy. Numilli aims to makes it easy to securely buy and sell bitcoin currency on the go using a mobile app and ATM machine. My ongoing responsibility is the design and branding for the mobile app, web platform and ATM machines

#### Freelance Designer

Foreminds · March 2017 - Present

BaseSight - workforce management platform, which aims to help improve efficiency and productivity. Responsibilities included aiding in the development of the initial concept by generating wireframes and initial interface designs

# **EDUCATION**

The University of Edinburgh · 2011 - 2015 Product design - 2:1 BA (Hons)

#### **DESIGN SKILLS**

Sketching
UI/UX Design
Interaction Design
Prototyping
Grid & Layout
Design Research
Visual Design

#### **DESIGN TOOLS**



Sketch



Craft



Illustrator

Ps

Photoshop

in

Invision



Pixate

#### DEVELOPMENT



 $\mathsf{HTML}$ 



Javascript



CSS